http://www.lagganlia.com/privacy-policy

Skip Nav
HOMEACCOMMODATION & FACILITIESEXPLORE CAIRNGORMSLagganlia lodgesLagganlia camping podsLagganlia main houseLagganlia event hire facilitiesCairngorms attractionsFind LagganliaOnsite activitiesEXPLORE ARGYLLBernice farmhouseBernice cottageBenmore main houseBenmore event hire facilities Argyll attractionsFind BenmoreWe are following advice from Scottish Government, Health Protection Scotland and the NHS. For the latest information on how this effects you or your booking please contact the relevant centre.Contact +EXPERIENCES & ACTIVITIESEXPLORE EXPERIENCESFamily and friendsSports clubsDuke of Edinburgh's AwardScouting and GuidingThird sectorSpecial interestCorporate and film locationsHoliday campsOutdoor learningEXPLORE ACTIVITIESOn footOn wheelsOn waterOn the edgeOn the slopesIn the field We are following advice from Scottish Government, Health Protection Scotland and the NHS. For the latest information on how this effects you or your booking please contact the relevant centre. Contact + OUTDOOR LEARNINGSCHOOL RESIDENTIALSAdventure Education CoreAdventure Education ExpeditionAdventure Education FieldAdventure Education FocusAdventure Education ActivityAdventure Education DesignResidential Late AvailabilityOutdoor Centres FAQsAWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTSDuke of EdinburghJASSJohn MuirECO schoolsEVENTS, COURSES AND CPDSchools and communitiesAwards and achievementsNational governing bodiesCEC excursionsAll eventsRESOURCES AND SERVICESOutdoor learning at homeSchools and communities resourcesTechnical and safetyConsultancy and commissioningEquipment and servicesCONTACTSBLOG
HOMEACCOMMODATION & FACILITIESEXPLORE CAIRNGORMSLagganlia lodgesLagganlia camping podsLagganlia main houseLagganlia event hire facilitiesCairngorms attractionsFind LagganliaOnsite activitiesEXPLORE ARGYLLBernice farmhouseBernice cottageBenmore main houseBenmore event hire facilities Argyll attractionsFind BenmoreEXPERIENCES & ACTIVITIESEXPLORE EXPERIENCESFamily and friendsSports clubsDuke of Edinburgh's AwardScouting and GuidingThird sectorSpecial interestCorporate and film locationsHoliday campsOutdoor learningEXPLORE ACTIVITIESOn footOn wheelsOn waterOn the edgeOn the slopesIn the fieldOUTDOOR LEARNINGSCHOOL RESIDENTIALSAdventure Education CoreAdventure Education ExpeditionAdventure Education FieldAdventure Education FocusAdventure Education ActivityAdventure Education DesignResidential Late AvailabilityOutdoor Centres FAQsAWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTSDuke of EdinburghJASSJohn MuirECO schoolsEVENTS, COURSES AND CPDSchools and communitiesAwards and achievementsNational governing bodiesCEC excursionsAll eventsRESOURCES AND SERVICESOutdoor learning at homeSchools and communities resourcesTechnical and safetyConsultancy and commissioningEquipment and servicesCONTACTSBLOG EXPERIENCE OUTDOORS PRIVACY NOTICE Overview This privacy notice explains how Experience Outdoors processes your information. If this privacy notice changes in any way, we will display an updated version. By regularly reviewing this page you will ensure you are aware of any changes. Data we collect We need basic information from you to carry out the task or service you have expressed an interest in. This is limited to your name, contact details and the nature of your booking/enquiry. At times, we will also record any additional information or details of special requests you submit. This will be held, where relevant, alongside your enquiry or booking details. We will ask for your consent when you join a mailing list. You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the unsubscribe option on any communication received from us, or by contacting us directly. We do not store any payment information; any online or phone payments are handled securely by Barclay Card Smart Pay. Why we need data We use the information to respond to your enquiry, manage your request or let you know about offers and news that we think may be of interest to you. We also use this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service. Also, we may use the information to improve our products and services. Information Sharing Your information will not be shared with any third parties, unless we are required to do so by law. Records retention and your rights We will not keep your information for any longer than it is needed, and will dispose of both paper and electronic records in a secure way. The length of time we need to keep information will depend on the purpose for which it is collected. The Council has a Record Retention Schedule which sets out how long we keep records and the reason why. Your right
to be informed about how we collect and use your personal information through privacy notices such as this. to request information we hold about you. This is known as a subject access request and is free of charge. We must respond within one month, although this can be extended to three months if the information is complex. to rectification. You are entitled to have your information rectified if it is factually inaccurate or incomplete. We must respond to your request within one month. If we decide to take no action, we will tell you why and let you know about your right of complaint to the UK Information Commissioner. to erasure. You have the right to ask us to delete your information or stop using it. It will not always be possible for us to comply with your request, for example if we have a legal obligation to keep the information. If we decide to take no action, we will tell you why and let you know about your right of complaint to the UK Information Commissioner. to restrict processing. You have the right to restrict how your data is processed in certain circumstances, for example if the information is not accurate. If a restriction is applied, we can retain just enough information to ensure that the restriction is respected in future. If we decide to lift a restriction on processing we must tell you. to data portability. If we are processing your personal data with your consent, and it is held in a structured, commonly used, machine readable form, you have a right to ask us to transmit it to another data controller so they can use it. This right does not apply if we process your personal data as part of our public task. to object. You can object to your information being used for profiling, direct marketing or research purposes. to automated decision making and profiling, to reduce the risk that a potentially damaging decision is taken without human intervention. To make a subject access request, or to exercise any of your rights, please contact the Council’s Information Rights Team. Collecting Information Automatically Our website uses cookies. Please see below for further information on what this means for you. Incidents, complaints and comments Experience Outdoors is part of the City of Edinburgh Council. More information about your rights under data protection legislation can be found on the Council website. If you have a request or require further information about the Experience Outdoors service, please contact
If you are concerned about what we do with your data, or think something has gone wrong, for example if you have received correspondence from the Council which is not addressed to you, contact the Council's Data Protection Officer to report a data protection incident. If you wish to make a complaint or comment about how we have processed your personal information, you can do so by writing to the Council's Data Protection Officer. If you are still unhappy with how the council have handled your complaint, you may contact UK Information Commissioner's Office Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire
SK9 5AF Tel: 08456 30 60 60 | Website: www.ico.org.uk(external link) Cookies Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. We use a combination of session cookies and persistent cookies to track how you use and experience our website, they build anonymous statistical data about how our website is performing and power the personalisation of the content to you. The types of cookie you can expect to see in use on our website are: A session cookie - commonly used to improve page load time or remember interactions, such as whether the user has already signed up to the mailing list. Pixel ratio - used to remember the pixel ratio of the device accessing the page. SharpSpring –manages automated emails and analyses user activity on our website, we use this to improve our service to you and ensure any marketing emails are relevant to you. Google Analytics- generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers and devices. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: www.google.com/policies/privacy/
About usContact usWork with usSupport usFind Lagganlia Find Benmore Our purpose Our partners Feedback NEWS & OFFERS Email(*)
Please enter a valid email
Interests
-SELECT YOUR MAIN INTEREST-AllAccommodation and facilitiesExperiences and activitiesOutdoor LearningOther Invalid Input
We will use the information you provide to send email updates on relevant news and promotions. You can unsubscribe via the link on any email received from us. We will not share your information or use it for any other purpose, unless we are required to do so by law. Read our Privacy Notice to find out how we process personal data and your information rights.
Submit
Submit
Investing in Outdoor Learning
BenmoreBenmore Outdoor Centre by Dunoon
Argyll PA23 8QX01369 706 337 BangholmBangholm Outdoor Centre 23 Craighall Gardens,
Edinburgh EH6 4RJ0131 551 4368 LagganliaLagganlia Outdoor Centre Feshiebridge
Kincraig PH21 1NG01540 651 265
Terms and ConditionsPrivacy Notice
